A Guide to the Moulse-Huff Genealogical Collection 1970s-1990s
Roanoke Public Libraries
- (Box 4)
  - Huff, I.M.: military service records various dates (Folder 2)
  - Huff, I. and E.: family group sheets, notes, newspaper articles and memorial booklets various dates (Folder 3)
  - Huff, Sparell: notes and family group sheets undated (Folder 4)
  - Huff, Isaac: Civil War records and gravesite information various dates (Folder 5)
  - Huff, R.A.: funeral record book, obituaries and photos various dates (Folder 6)
  - Huff, H.T.: photos and negatives of funeral unknown date (Folder 7)
  - Huff, Henry T.: Norfolk and Western Magazine retirement article June 1949 (Folder 8)
  - Huff, H.T.: funeral record book, obituary, photos and correpondence various dates (Folder 9)
  - Huff, H.T.: marriage certificate, birth certificate and other original documents various dates (Folder 10)
  - Huff, Helen: documents various dates (Folder 11)
  - Huff, Fred L.: documents various dates (Folder 12)
  - Huff, K.H.: pedigree chart, family group sheets, marriage license and photos various dates (Folder 13)
  - Huff, F.H.: army discharge papers, handwritten biography, drivers license, identification cards and estate settlement various dates (Folder 14)
  - Huff, Henry and Rosa: birth, marriage and death documents various dates (Folder 15)
  - Huff, J.: DAR gravestone, correspondence, newspaper articles and receipts various dates (Folder 16)
  - Huff, John Sr.: correspondence regarding DAR headstone and Mary Gearhart-Snuffer Family various dates (Folder 17)
  - Huff, J.: research on Bucks County, Pennsylvania residency and correspondence various dates (Folder 18)
  - Huff, J. Sr.: biography written by Helen Huff Moulse undated (Folder 19)
  - Huff, J.: list of documents related to John Huff undated (Folder 20)
  - Huff, J. and E.: accounts, dower and inventory of estate various dates (Folder 21)
  - Sparell-Griffith: guardianship of Huff children undated (Folder 22)
  - Huff, J.: biography, family group sheets, DAR membership for Helen Huff Moulse, newspaper articles and marriage records various dates (Folder 23)
  - Huff, J.: Huff vs. Ferguson court case explanation undated (Folder 24)
  - Huff, J.: Huff vs. Ferguson - copies of court case documents various dates (Folder 25)
  - Huff, G.W.: unfinished hotel and Floyd/Franklin newspaper article various dates (Folder 26)
  - Huff, O.: Claudill House in Floyd County newspaper article unknown date (Folder 27)
  - Huff, I.: Huff House in Roanoke County newspaper article unknown date (Folder 28)
  - Huff, P.: Monterey - newspaper articles on house and house tour booklet various dates (Folder 29)
  - Huff: Valley View Mall newspaper articles various dates (Folder 30)
  - Hough-Huff: handwritten copy of family history undated (Folder 31)
  - Hough-Huff: "The Name and Family of Hough and Huff" by Roots Research Bureau undated (Folder 32)
  - Hough-Huff: ancestral file, notes and family group sheet undated (Folder 33)
  - Hough-Huff: family group sheets, notes and biography of John Huff undated (Folder 34)
  - Hough-Huff: census data and notes various dates (Folder 35)
  - Hough-Huff: ancestral files, maps, family group sheets, notes and Roanoke marriages various dates (Folder 36)
  - Hough-Huff: notes undated (Folder 37)
  - Hough-Huff: pedigree chart and family group sheets including other families undated (Folder 38)
  - Hough-Huff: census information, pedigree charts and notes undated (Folder 39)
  - Hough-Huff: family history compilation and family group sheets undated (Folder 40)
  - Hough: property inventory and correspondence various dates (Folder 41)
  - Hough: family group sheets undated (Folder 42)
  - Huff-Ames: original marriage certificate unknown (Folder 43)
  - Huff-Ames: birth certificate request, deeds for Salem property, and photos of Camp Lee, Virginia various dates (Folder 44)
  - Huff-Carder: notes, copy of will, land records, ancestral file, marriage records, family group sheets and pedigree chart various dates (Folder 45)
  - Huff-Cannaday: family group sheets, correspondence, newspaper articles, notes and records request various dates (Folder 46)
  - Huff-Cannaday: pedigree chart, military service records and notes various dates (Folder 47)
  - Huff-Cannaday: excerpts from "Wingfield's Works" and marriage list various dates (Folder 48)
  - Huff-Cannaday: family group sheets undated (Folder 49)
  - Huff-Cannaday: correspondence and John Huff Sr. DAR various dates (Folder 50)
  - Cannaday-Huff: notes, obituaries, carte de viste of Fred Heller various dates (Folder 51)
  - Cannaday-Huff: family group sheets and notes undated (Folder 52)
  - Cannaday-Huff: notes and records various dates (Folder 53)
  - Cannaday-Huff: family group sheets, pedigree chart, memorial booklets, obituaries, notes and marriage license various dates (Folder 54)
  - Cannaday-Huff: family group sheets, newspaper articles, obituaries, notes and correspondence various dates (Folder 55)
  - Cannaday: book excerpts and notes undated (Folder 56)
  - Cannaday: obituaries and memorial booklets various dates (Folder 57)
  - Cannaday: bookm excerpts undated (Folder 58)
  - Cannaday-Huff: copy of bond 1847 (Folder 59)
  - Cannaday: photos of cemeteries in Floyd and Tazewell County, Virginia undated (Folder 60)
  - Cannaday, Peter: family group sheets, pedigree charts, obituaries and correspondence various dates (Folder 61)
  - Cannaday-Ingram: family group sheets, notes and book excerpts undated (Folder 62)
  - Cannaday-Turner-Prillaman-Huff: family group sheets, pedigree chart, book excerpts and notes various dates (Folder 63)
  - Cannaday: notes undated (Folder 64)
  - Cannaday-Prillaman: family group sheets undated (Folder 65)
  - Prillaman-Sowers: notes, pedigree charts and book excerpts undated (Folder 66)
  - Sowers: family group sheets and correspondence various dates (Folder 67)
  - Moore-Prillaman: family group sheets, notes, book excerpts undated (Folder 68)
  - Akers-Cannaday: photocopy of book, "The Akers Family of Franklin County, Virginia Combined with Boone, Cannaday..." undated (Folder 69)
  - Cannaday-Thomas: correspondence, notes and John Huff DAR headstone and family group sheets various dates (Folder 70)
  - Turner-Cannaday: book excerpts and notes undated (Folder 71)
  - Dillman-Jones-Huff: notes, census records and marriage listings various dates (Folder 72)
- (Box 5)
  - Early-Cannaday-Adams: contains notes on Bedford County wills various dates (Folder 1)
  - Early: family reunion photos 1990-1992 (Folder 2)
  - Early: family group sheets, newspaper articles, obituaries, correspondence and a marriage license various dates (Folder 3)
  - Early: newspaper articles, notes, memorial booklets and photos various dates (Folder 4)
  - Early: Franklin County history excerpt undated (Folder 5)
  - Early-Richardson: family group sheets, book excerpts undated (Folder 6)
  - Simmons-Early-Keys-Richardson: family group sheets, notes and memorial booklets various dates (Folder 7)
  - Gearhart-Turner-Adams-Huff: notes undated (Folder 8)
  - Gearhart-Huff: correspondence between J. Wood Jr. and G. Huff various dates (Folder 9)
  - Gearhart: notes undated (Folder 10)
  - Gearhart: photos of grave markers undated (Folder 11)
  - Gearhart: family group sheets, correspondence and notes various dates (Folder 12)
  - Gearhart-Gerhart-Gearheart: correspondence and notes various dates (Folder 13)
  - Huff-Gearhart-Early: "A Brief of Wills and Marriages in Montgomery and Fincastle County" with notes 1731-1831 (Folder 14)
  - Huff-Gearhart: family group sheets, notes and marriage license various dates (Folder 15)
  - Huff-Gearhart: notes, headstone photos, biography, marriage records and SAR papers various dates (Folder 16)
  - Grubb-Richardson-Mowles: notes undated (Folder 17)
  - Grubb: pedigree chart, family group sheets, notes and obituaries various dates (Folder 18)
  - Grubb: family group sheets various dates (Folder 19)
  - Grubb-Thompson-Anderson-Hamilton-Mowles: family group sheets and newspaper articles various dates (Folder 20)
  - Heller, Frank: certificate from American Viscose Corporation 1947 (Folder 21)
  - Horne: pedigree charts, marriage documents, photos, notes and obituaries various dates (Folder 22)
  - Horne: family group sheets, notes, marriage records, military service records and biography excerpt various dates (Folder 23)
  - Austin: book excerpt and notes undated (Folder 24)
  - Horne: pedigree chart, correspondence, family group sheets, notes and photos various dates (Folder 25)
  - Horne, J.: pedigree chart and family group sheet various dates (Folder 26)
  - Horne: family group sheets and notes various dates (Folder 27-28)
  - Johnson-Huff: family group sheets, notes and obituaries various dates (Folder 29)
  - Johnston-Richardson: pedigree chart and family group sheets various dates (Folder 30)
  - Huff-Knowles: notes undated (Folder 31)
  - Huff-Knowles: notes and book excerpt listing wills various dates (Folder 32)
  - Knowles: notes undated (Folder 33)
  - Knowles: printed transcription of family Bible record various dates (Folder 34)
  - Huff-Livesly: family group sheets, ancestral files, newspaper articles, photos and notes various dates (Folder 35)
  - Richardson-Horne-Early: book excerpt, notes, newspaper articles, obituaries and photos various dates (Folder 36)
  - Richardson-Horne: photos, notes, newspaper articles and obituaries various dates (Folder 37)
  - Richardson-Horne: notes undated (Folder 38)
  - Richardson-Horne: pedigree charts, marriage documents, family group sheets and obituaries various dates (Folder 39)
  - Richardson-Horne: family photo, family group sheets, pedigree chart and memorial booklets various dates (Folder 40)
  - Huff-Richardson-Horne-Mattox: photos and notes undated (Folder 41)
  - Huff-Richardson-Horne: family history compiled by Helen Huff Moulse undated (Folder 42)
  - Huff-Richardson: family tree and census information various dates (Folder 43)
  - Huff-Richardson: pedigree chart and notes various dates (Folder 44)
  - Huff-Richardson: Civil War service records various dates (Folder 45)
  - Richardson: marriage documents various dates (Folder 46)
  - Richardson: obituaries, memorial booklets and newspaper articles various dates (Folder 47)
  - Richardson: copies of receipts 1880-1889 (Folder 48)
  - Keys-Richardson: notes undated (Folder 49)
  - Richardson: pedigree charts and family group sheets various dates (Folder 50)
  - Richardson: photos, marriage announcements, notes, memorial booklets and obituaries various dates (Folder 51)
  - Richardson: marriage records, death certificates, coat of arms and newspaper articles various dates (Folder 52)
  - Richardson: family group sheets and census records various dates (Folder 53)
  - Richardson, H.: photos and negatives of gathering 1992 (Folder 54)
  - Richardson-Littrell: pedigree chart, family group sheets, newspaper articles and notes various dates (Folder 55)
  - Littrell, Robert and Daisy: photo of 50th Wedding Anniversary unknown date (Folder 56)
  - Richardson-Johnston: memorial booklets various dates (Folder 57)
  - Richardson-Wineman: family group sheets, notes and book excerpts various dates (Folder 58)
  - Richardson-Dillman-Early: notes from Botetourt County census and list of children various dates (Folder 59)
  - Hough-Huff-Snuffer: ancestral file, family group sheets and notes various dates (Folder 60)
  - Huff-Snuffer: correspondence various dates (Folder 61)
  - Snuffer: notes undated (Folder 62)
  - Neighbors-Nabors: newspaper articles, research request and brochure various dates (Folder 63)
  - Neighbors-Sirry-Aliff: notes, family group sheets and newspaper articles various dates (Folder 64)
  - Neighbors-Sirry-Leffler: family group sheets, pedigree charts and obituaries various dates (Folder 65)
  - Neighbors-Leffler: notes, memorial booklets, obituaries and photos various dates (Folder 66)
  - Olds-Moore: obituaries and memorial booklets various dates (Folder 67)
  - Smith-Saunders-Sparell: pedigree charts, family group sheets, notes, photos and marriage license various dates (Folder 68)
  - Unidentified family photos, including Col. Oliver North undated (Folder 69)
  - Unidentified family group photos undated (Folder 70)
  - Southwestern Virginia Genealogical Society: membership directory and brochure (Folder 71)
  - Photos and negatives of Southwestern Virginia undated (Folder 72)
  - Photos and negatives of courthouse in Martinsville, Virginia undated (Folder 73)
  - Photos and negatives of Fincastle and Botetourt County, Virginia undated (Folder 74)
  - Notes on cemeteries in Catawba and Roanoke County, Virginia undated (Folder 75)
  - Roanoke area genealogy efforts undated (Folder 76)
  - "The Salem Story", program 1952 (Folder 77)
  - First Christian Church - Salem, Virginia: dedication program, directory, bulletins and newspaper articles various dates (Folder 78)
  - Odd Fellows Lodge - Salem, Virginia: member directory and newspaper articles various dates (Folder 79)
  - Ridgeway Baptist Church - Salem, Virginia: church history, program, photos and newsletters various dates (Folder 80)
  - Ridgeway Baptist Church - Salem, Virginia: directories, by-laws and constitution various dates (Folder 81)
  - Ridgeway Baptist Church - Salem, Virginia: newspaper articles various dates (Folder 82)
  - Negatives of McAlerando-Sisk House in Lake Spring Park, Salem, Virginia undated (Folder 83)
- (Box 6)
  - Moulse-Mowles: family tree charts undated (Folder 1)
  - Moulse-Knowles: election sign and photocopies of wills various dates (Folder 2)
  - Adams: photocopies of wills, marriages, etc. various dates (Folder 3)
  - Huff: photocopies of wills, census records, marriage records and notes various dates (Folder 4)
  - Cannaday-Ingram: photocopies of wills various dates (Folder 5)
  - Historic image of Longwood Park House in Salem, Virginia undated (Folder 6)
- (Box 7)
  - Scrapbook: Moulse-Mowles family reunion photos and reunion committee notes 1979-1985 (Item 1)